Guide to the Stanford University, Press, Archival Book Copies
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Pre-1966
  - Muench, George A, An Evaluation of non-directive psychotherapy: by means of the Rorschach and other indices., 1947
  - Mullendore, William Clinton, 1892-, History of the United States Food administration, 1917-1919., 1941
  - Munroe, Ruth Learned, Prediction of the adjustment and academic performance of college students by a modification of the Rorschach method., 1945
  - Myers, Earl Hamlet, Biology, ecology and morphogenesis of a pelagic foraminifer., 1943
  - Myers, George S. (George Sprague), 1905-1985, The primary groups of oviparous cyprinodont fishes., 1931
  - Nabuco, Carolina, The life of Joaquim Nabuco., 1950 (Box 47)
  - Nahm, Helen, Title: An Evaluation of selected schools of nursing with respect to certain educational objectives., 1948
  - Nasatir, Abraham Phineas, French activities in California; an archival calendar-guide., 1945 (Box 47)
  - National Academy of Sciences (U.S.). Special Committee on Airships, Report No. 3 Technical Aspects of the Loss of the Macon., 1936 (Box 47)
  - Neidig, William J. (William Jonathan), 1870-1955, The first wardens., 1901
  - Neilson, Donald W, Swimming pools for schools., 1954
  - Nestev, I. V. (Izrail' Vladimirovich), 1911-, Prokofiev., 1960 (Box 47)
  - Neuhaus, Eugen, 1879-1963, The history and ideals of American art., 1931
  - Neumark, Solomon Daniel, 1899-, Economic influence on the South African frontier, 1652-1836., 1957
  - New, John F. H, Anglican and Puritan: the basis of their opposition, 1558-1640., 1964 (Box 48)
  - Newman, Frances Burks, The adolescent in social groups; studies in the observation of personality., 1946
  - Newman, Henry Wise, 1907-, Acute alcoholic intoxication, a critical review., 1941
  - Nivison, David S, Confucianism in action., 1959 (Box 48)
  - Noble, Glenn Arthur, 1909-, A brief anatomy of the turtle., 1940
  - North, Robert Carver, Kuomintang and Chinese communist elites., 1952
  - North, Robert Carver, Moscow and Chinese Communists., 1963
  - North, Robert Carver, Moscow and Chinese Communists., 1953
  - O'Bryan, Joseph Grattan, Washington form book; forms and suggestions for Washington practice., 1932
  - O'Neil, R. G. (LRobert Grant), 1905-, The Stanford axe, 1899-1930.
  - Oliver, Peter, Peter Oliver's Origin & progress of the American Rebellion a Tory view., 1961 (Box 48)
  - Olkin, Ingram, editor, Contributions to probability and statistics; essays in honor of Harold Hotelling., 1960
  - Ophuls, William, 1871-1933, A statistical survey of three thousand autopsies, from the Department of pathology of the Stanford university medical school., 1926
  - Ophuls, William, 1871-1933, Arteriosclerosis cardiovascular disease: their relation to infectious diseases., 1921
  - Ophuls, William, 1871-1933, The Pathology of nephritis: as illustrated by thirty-two consecutive cases., 1916
  - Osborn, Sarah, 1693-1775, Letters of Sarah Byng Osborn, 1721-1773, from the collection of the Hon. Mrs. McDonnel., 1930 (Box 48)
  - Owens, W. B. (William Brownlee), b. 1887, Forms and suggestions for California practice., 1930
  - Pacific Arts Association, Proceedings of the Pacific Arts Association., 1926
  - Packer, Herbert L, Ex-Communist witnesses: four studies in fact finding., 1962 (Box 48)
  - Padover, Saul Kussiel, 1905-, French institutions: values and politics., 1954
  - Paris Symposium on Radio Astronomy (1958), Paris Symposium on Radio Astronomy, IAU symposium no. 9 and URSI symposium no. 1 held from 30 July to 6 August 1958., 1959
  - Parks, George Bruner, 1890-, The English traveler to Italy., 1954
  - Patrick, David Lyall, 1899-, The textual history of Richard III., 1936
  - Patrick, Mary Mills, 1850-1940, A Bosporus adventure; Istanbul (Constantinople) woman's college, 1871-1924., 1934
  - Paul, John, 1922-, Cell biology., 1964 (Box 48)
  - Paul, John, 1922-, Cell biology., 1965 (Box 48)
  - Paulding, James Kirke, 1778-1860, The lion of the West: retitled The Kentuckian, or A trip to New York. A farce in two acts., 1954
  - Payne, George Louis, Britain's scientific and technological manpower., 1960 (Box 48)
  - Payne, Stanley G, Falange; a history of Spanish fascism., 1961 (Box 48)
  - Payne, Stanley G, Falange; a history of Spanish fascism., 1965 (Box 48)
  - Pearson, Lionel Ignacius Cusack, Popular ethics in ancient Greece., 1962
  - Pearson, Lu Emily Hess, Elizabethans at home., 1957 (Box 49)
  - Peatman, John Gray and Tore Hallonquist, The patterning of listener attitudes toward radio broadcasts; methods and results., 1945
  - Peffer, E. Louise, The closing of the public domain: disposal and reservation policies, 1900-50., 1951 (Box 49)
  - Peirce, Charles S. (Charles Sanders), 1839-1914, Values in a universe of chance; selected writings of Charles S. Peirce., 1958 (Box 49)
  - Pepinsky, Harold B, The Selection and use of diagnostic categories in clinical counseling., 1948
  - Perceval, John, fl., 1840-1860, Perceval's narrative: a patient's account of his psychosis, 1830-1832., 1961 (Box 49)
  - Perez Galdos, Benito, 1843-1920, Juan Martin el Empecinado., 1929
  - Perez Lugin, Alejandro, 1870-1926, La casa de la Troya., 1930
  - Persons, Christopher Edgar, Public relations for colleges and universities; a manual of practical procedure., 1946 (Box 49)
  - Peterson, Martin Severin, 1897-, Joaquin Miller, literary frontiersman., 1937
  - Phillips, Helen Anabel, J. M. Keynes, vision and technique., 1951
  - Pickwell, Gayle, Amphibians and reptiles of the Pacific states., 1947 (Box 49)
  - Pintner, Rudolf et. al, Supplementary guide for the revised Stanford-Binet scale (form L)., 1944
  - Plowman, E. Grosvenor, Elements of business logistics., 1964 (Box 73)
  - Poleman, Thomas T, The Papaloapan project; agricultural development in the Mexican tropics., 1964
  - Pomeroy, Earl S, Pacific outpost; American strategy in Guam and Micronesia., 1951 (Box 49)
  - Pool, Ithiel de Sola, 1917-, Satellite generals: a study of military elites in the Soviet sphere., 1955
  - Pool, Ithiel de Sola, 1917-, Symbols of democracy., 1952
  - Pool, Ithiel de Sola, 1917-, Symbols of internationalism., 1951 (Box 49)
  - Pool, Ithiel de Sola, 1917-, The "prestige papers": a survey of their editorials., 1952
  - Portland Art Museum, Native arts of the Pacific Northwest, from the Rasmussen collection of the Portland Art Museum., 1949 (Box 47)
  - Portland Art Museum (Or.), Native arts of the Pacific Northwest, from the Rasmussen collection of the Portland Art Museum., 1954
  - Price, John B, Familiar birds of the Stanford campus., 1954 (Box 49)
  - Price, John B, Familiar birds of the Stanford campus., 1931 (Box 49)
  - Proctor, William Martin, 1875-1937, The junior high school, its organization and administration., 1930
  - Prosser, Eleanor, Drama and religion in the English mystery plays: a re-evaluation., 1961 (Box 49)
  - Pryor, Helen Brenton, 1897-, Width-weight tables for boys and girls from 1 to 16 years, for men and women from 17 to 24 years., 1937
  - Pryor, Helen Brenton, 1897-, Width-weight tables, for boys and girls from 1 to 16 years, for men and women from 18 to 41+ years., 1940
  - Pumpian-Mindlin, Eugene, 1908-1976, Psychoanalysis as science: the Hixon lectures on the scientific status of psychoanalysis., 1952 (Box 50)
  - Purcell, Victor, Malaya: Communist or free?., 1954 (Box 50)
  - Puryear, Vernon John, 1901-, International economics and diplomacy in the Near East; a study of British commercial policy in the Levant, 1834-1853., 1935
  - Radius, Walter Albrecht, United States shipping in Transpacific trade, 1922-1938., 1944 (Box 50)
  - Rael, Juan Bautista, Cuentos españoles de Colorado y Nuevo Méjico. Vol. I and II., 1957 (Box 50)
  - Rael, Juan Bautista, The New Mexican alabado., 1951
  - Ralston, Jackson H. (Jackson Harvey), 1857-1945, An unshackled civilization., 1930 (Box 50)
  - Ralston, Jackson H. (Jackson Harvey), 1857-1945, International arbitration, from Athens to Locarno., 1929 (Box 50)
  - Ralston, Jackson H. (Jackson Harvey), 1857-1945, Supplement to 1926 revised edition of The Law and procedure of international tribunals., 1936
  - Ralston, Jackson H. (Jackson Harvey), 1857-1945, The law and procedure of international tribunals., 1926 (Box 50)
  - Ramaswamy, M, The creative ns2:role of the Supreme Court of the United States., 1956 (Box 51)
  - Rappaport, Armin, The British press and Wilsonian neutrality., 1951
  - Rathbun, Harry J. (Harry John), 1894-, The Anglo-American legal system., 1941
  - Reed, Alfred Cummings, Handbook of tropical medicine., 1943
  - Reed, Nelson, The Caste War of Yucatan., 1964 (Box 51)
  - Reid, John Turner, Modern Spain and liberalism; a study in literary contrasts., 1937
  - Reiss, Richard F, Neural theory and modeling; proceedings of the 1962 Ojai symposium., 1964 (Box 51)
  - Rendtorff, Karl Gustave, Aids to German prose composition., 1900
  - Rensch, Hero Eugene, 1889-, Historic spots in California: the southern counties., 1932 (Box 51)
  - Rensch, Hero Eugene, 1889-, Historic spots in California: valley and Sierra counties., 1933 (Box 51)
  - Resnikoff, George J, Tables of the non-central t-distribution: density function, cumulative distribution function, and percentage points., 1957
  - Ribera, Julian, 1858-1934, Music in ancient Arabia and Spain; being La musica de las Cantigas., 1929
  - Richards, Lawrence Wayne, 1901-, Geologic history at a glance., 1934
  - Ricketts, Edward Flanders, 1896-1948, Between Pacific tides: an account of the habits and habitats of some five hundred of the common, conspicuous seashore invertebrates of the Pacific Coast between Sitka, Alaska, and northern Mexico; 3rd ed., rev. / revisions by Joel W. Hedgpeth., 1962
  - Ricketts, Edward Flanders, 1896-1948, Between Pacific tides; an account of the habits and habitats of some five hundred of the common, conspicuous seashore invertebrates of the Pacific coast between Sitka, Alaska, and northern Mexico; 3d ed., rev. by Joel W. Hedgpeth., 1952
  - Ricketts, Edward Flanders, 1897-1948, Between Pacific tides.., 1939
  - Ridgway, John Livesy, 1859-, Scientific illustration., 1938
  - Rivers, Thomas M. (Thomas Milton), 1888-1962, Viruses and virus diseases., 1939
  - Roberts, Helen M, Big Chief Solano: a tale of Mission San Francisco Solano., 1948
  - Roberts, Helen M, Pasquala of Santa Ines: a tale of Mission Santa Ines., 1948
  - Roberts, Helen M, The two-tailed comet: a tale of Mission San Juan Capistrano., 1948
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene, The new United States., 1946 (Box 51)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene, They voted for Roosevelt; the Presidential vote, 1932-1944., 1947 (Box 51)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene, 1887-, American democracy in time of crisis., 1934 (Box 51)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene, 1887-, Independent study in the Lower division at Stanford University, 1931-1937. (Box 51)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene, 1887-, The presidential vote, 1896-1932., 1934 (Box 52)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene, 1887-, The presidential vote, 1896-1932., 1947 (Box 52)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene, 1887-, The presidential vote, 1936, supplementing The presidential vote, 1896-1932., 1940
  - Roll of Ipsden, Eric Roll, Baron, 1907-, The Combined Food Board; a study in wartime international planning., 1956
  - Romero, José Luis, 1909-, A history of Argentine political thought., 1963 (Box 72)
  - Rosenberg, Edgar, From Shylock to Svengali; Jewish stereotypes in English fiction., 1960 (Box 52)
  - Rosenberg, Solomon Leopold Millard, 1869-1934, A brief anthology of Mexican verse., 1928
  - Ross, G. A. Johnston, Behavior and destiny: a Christian view., 1931
  - Rothschild, Salomon de, baron, 1835-1864, A casual view of America; the home letters of Salomon de Rothschild, 1859-1861., 1961 (Box 52)
  - Roucek, Joseph Slabey, Balkan politics: international relations in no man's land., 1948 (Box 52)
  - Rowntree, Lester, Flowering shrubs of California and their value to the gardener., 1939
  - Ruellan, André, Local government in Japan., 1965
  - Ruppenthal, Karl M, Developments in business logistics., 1964 (Box 73)
  - Russell, Carl Parcher, 1894-1967, One hundred years in Yosemite; the romantic story of early human affairs in the central Sierra Nevada., 1931
  - Russell, Frances Theresa Peet, 1873-1936, One word more on Browning., 1927 (Box 52)
  - Russell, Frank Marion, 1886-, The Saar: battleground and pawn., 1951 (Box 52)
  - Rutherford, Andrew, 1929-, Byron, a critical study., 1961 (Box 52)
  - Rutherford, Andrew, 1929-, Kipling's mind and art, selected critical essays., 1964
  - Ryan, Lawrence V, Roger Ascham., 1963 (Box 53)
  - Safley, James Clifford, Fisherman's pier., 1948
  - Sage, Bruce H, Volumetric and phase behavior of hydrocarbons., 1949 (Box 53)
  - Salvemini, Gaetano, 1873-1957, Mazzini.
  - Sands, Lester Bruton, History of education chart., 1957
  - Sands, Lester Bruton, History of education chart., 1939
  - Sands, Lester Bruton, History of education chart., 1949
  - Sanford, Fernando, 1854-1948, Bulletin of the Terrestrial Electric Observatory of Fernando Sanford, Palo Alto, California., 1923
  - Sanford, Fernando, b. 1854, Terrestrial electricity, by Fernando Sanford., 1931 (Box 53)
  - Sansom, George Bailey, Sir, 1883-1965, A history of Japan., 1958
  - Santivan, Fernando, 1886-1973, La hechizada., 1929
  - Savelle, Max, This is my America (2 cc)., 1948 (Box 53)
  - Savitskii, E. M. (Evgenii Mikhailovich), The influence of temperature on the mechanical properties of metals and alloys., 1961 (Box 53)
  - Scaff, Alvin H, The Philippine answer to communism., 1955 (Box 53)
  - Scarf, Herbert E, Multistage inventory models and techniques., 1963 (Box 53)
  - Schachter, Stanley, 1922-, The psychology of affiliation; experimental studies of the sources of gregariousness., 1959 (Box 53)
  - Scheffer, Victor B, Seals, sea lions, and walruses; a review of the Pinnipedia., 1958
  - Schenck, Hubert G, California fossils for the field geologist., 1950
  - Schenck, Hubert G. (Hubert Gregory), 1897-1960, California fossils for the field geologist., 1940
  - Schenck, Hubert G. (Hubert Gregory), 1897-1960, Significance of Lepidocyclina (Lepidocyclina) Californica, new species, in the Vaqueros formation (Tertiary), California., 1942
  - Schenk, Edward T, Procedure in taxonomy., 1948 (Box 54)
  - Schenk, Edward T. (Edward Theodore), 1905-, Procedure in taxonomy, including a reprint in translation of the Règles internationales de la nomenclature zoölogique (International code of zoölogical nomenclature) with titles and notes on the opinions rendered to the present date (1907 to 1956) 3d ed. enl. and in part rewritten by A. Myra Keen and Siemon William Muller.
  - Schenk, Edward T. (Edward Theodore), 1905-, Procedure in taxonomy, including a reprint of the International rules of zoological nomenclature with summaries of Opinions rendered to the present date;., 1936
  - School Mathematics Study Group, Calculus; student text; Prelim. ed., 1964
  - Schramm, Wilbur Lang, 1907-, Mass media and national development; the ns2:role of information in the developing countries., 1964 (Box 54)
  - Schramm, Wilbur Lang, 1907-, One day in the world's press; fourteen great newspapers on a day of crisis, November 2, 1956., 1959
  - Schramm, Wilbur Lang, 1907-, Television in the lives of our children., 1961 (Box 53)
  - Schramm, Wilbur Lang, 1907-, The people look at educational television; a report of nine representative ETV stations., 1963 (Box 54)
  - Schueller, George Konrad, 1917-, The Politburo., 1951 (Box 54)
  - Schultz, Edwin W, A Laboratory manual of medical bacteriology., 1946
  - Schwab, Arnold T, James Gibbons Huneker, critic of the seven arts., 1963 (Box 54)
  - Schwartz, William Leonard, 1888-, The sententiae in the dramas of Corneille., 1939 (Box 54)
  - Schwartz, William Leonard, 1888-, ed, Atala, or the love and constancy of two savages in the desert., 1930 (Box 54)
  - Scitovsky, Tibor, Economic theory and western European integration., 1962
  - Scitovsky, Tibor, Economic theory and western European integration., 1958
  - Scitovsky, Tibor, Papers on welfare and growth., 1964 (Box 54)
  - Scott, Flora Murray, Introduction to the limnology of Searsville Lake., 1927
  - Scoyen, Eivind T, The rainbow canyons., 1931
  - Searles, Colbert, ed, Catalogue de tous les liveres fe few M. Chapelain., 1912 (Box 61)
  - Sears, Jesse B, School administration in the twentieth century., 1934
  - Sears, Jesse Brundage, Cubberley of Stanford and his contribution to American education., 1957 (Box 54)
  - Sears, Robert R, Identification and child rearing., 1965 (Box 55)
  - Sears, Robert R, Patterns of child rearing., 1957 (Box 54)
  - Secrist, Horace, b. 1881, Banking ratios; a study of the operating results of member banks with special reference to the twelfth Federal reserve district, and to California., 1930 (Box 55)
  - Sefton, Alice Allene, The Women's Division, National Amateur Athletic Federation; sixteen years of progress in athletics for girls and women, 1923-1939., 1941 (Box 72)
  - Seidensticker, Edward, 1921-, Kaf¯u the Scribbler; the life and writings of Nagai Kaf¯u, 1879-1959., 1965 (Box 55)
  - Seneca, Lucius Annaeus, ca. 4 B.C.-65 A.D, Ad Lucilium epistulae morales, with an English translation by Richard M. Gummere. In three volumns., 1917
  - Sensabaugh, George F., et. al., The Study of English in California schools., 1952
  - Sensabaugh, George Frank, The tragic muse of John Ford., 1944 (Box 55)
  - Sensabaugh, George Frank, 1906-, That grand Whig, Milton., 1952 (Box 55)
  - Settle, Raymond W, Empire on wheels., 1949 (Box 55)
  - Seward, Samuel Swayze, 1876-1932, The paradox of the ludicrous., 1930 (Box 55)
  - Seward, Samuel Swayze, Jr., 1876-1932, Reference sheets for English composition., 1923
  - Shafer, George D, The ways of a mud dauber., 1949 (Box 55)
  - Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616, Much ado about nothing. Edited by Alphonso Gerald Newcomer. Completed by Henry David Gray., 1929
  - Sharpey-Schafer, E. A., An Introduction to the study of the endocrine glands and internal secretions., 1914
  - Sharples, Ada White, Alaska wild flowers., 1938 (Box 55)
  - Shên, Tsung-lien, Tibet and the Tibetans., 1953 (Box 56)
  - Shevky, Eshref, Social area analysis; theory, illustrative application, and computational procedures., 1955
  - Shock, Nathan Wetherill, 1906-, A classified bibliography of gerontology and geriatrics., 1951 (Box 56)
  - Shock, Nathan Wetherill, 1906-, A classified bibliography of gerontology and geriatrics; Supplement., 1957
  - Shock, Nathan Wetherill, 1906-, Trends in gerontology., 1957 (Box 56)
  - Shock, Nathan Wetherill, 1906-, Trends in gerontology., 1951 (Box 56)
  - Shreve, Forrest, 1878-1950, Vegetation and flora of the Sonoran Desert. V. I and II., 1964 (Box 57)
  - Shutes, Milton H, Lincoln and California., 1943
  - Siegel, Bernard J. (Bernard Joseph), 1913-, Acculturation: critical abstracts, North America., 1955
  - Simon, Brian, Educational psychology in the U.S.S.R., 1963 (Box 56)
  - Simon, Brian, Psychology in the U.S.S.R., 1957 (Box 56)
  - Skinner, Elliott Percival, 1924-, The Mossi of the Upper Volta; the political development of a Sudanese people., 1964 (Box 57)
  - Sloan, Richard E., 1857-, Memories of an Arizona judge., 1932 (Box 56)
  - Slonaker, James Rollin, b. 1866, The effect of different percentages of protein in the diet of six generations of rats., 1939
  - Slusser, Robert M, A calendar of Soviet treaties: 1917-1957., 1959
  - Smith, Albert W, Elementary Machine Design., 1895 (Box 57)
  - Smith, Charles Piper, 1877-, A distributional catalogue of the lupines of Oregon., 1927
  - Smith, Dama Margaret, Hopi girl., 1931
  - Smith, Dama Margaret, I married a ranger., 1930
  - Smith, Dama Margaret, Indian tribes of the Southwest., 1933
  - Smith, Frances Rand, The Mission of San Antonio de Padua California., 1932 (Box 57)
  - Smith, Gilbert Morgan, 1885-1959, Marine algae of the Monterey Peninsula, California., 1964 (Box 57)
  - Smith, Henry Clay, Music in relation to employee attitudes, piecework production, and industrial accidents., 1947
  - Smith, Herbert G. (Herbert Getchell), 1890-, Figuring with graphs and scales., 1938
  - Smith, Paul Jordan, 1885-, Bibliographia Burtoniana; a study of Robert Burton's The anatomy of melancholy, with a bibliography of Burton's writings., 1931
  - Smith, Thomas C, Political change and industrial development in Japan: government enterprise, 1868-1880., 1965
  - Smith, Thomas C, Political change and industrial development in Japan: government enterprise, 1868-1880., 1955
  - Smith, Thomas C, The agrarian origins of modern Japan., 1959 (Box 57)
  - Smythe, Hugh H, The new Nigerian elite., 1960 (Box 57)
  - Snedden, Genevra S, Mountain Cattle and Frontier People; stories of the Snedden family., 1947 (Box 58)
  - Snyder, Rixford Kinney, The tariff problem in Great Britain, 1918-1923., 1944
  - Sokel, Walter Herbert, 1917-, The writer in extremis; expressionism in twentieth-century German literature., 1959 (Box 58)
  - Sokolnikov, G. IA. (Grigorii IAkovlevich), Soviet policy in public finance, 1917-1928., 1931
  - Solomon, Herbert, 1919-, Studies in item analysis and prediction., 1961 (Box 58)
  - Solt, Leo F, Saints in arms; puritanism and democracy in Cromwell's army., 1959
  - Sooy, Louise Pinkney, Plan your own home., 1946 (Box 58)
  - Sooy, Louise Pinkney, 1889-, Plan your own home., 1940
  - Spindler, George Dearborn, Education and anthropology., 1955
  - Spoehr, Herman Augustus, 1885-1954, Essays on science., 1956 (Box 58)
  - Staley, William Wesley, 1898-, Introduction to mine surveying; 2d ed., 1964 (Box 58)
  - Standard Oil Company of California, The functions of corporate secretaries, treasurers, and comptrollers: a survey of corporate practices., 1944
  - Stanford Conference on Business Education, Proceedings of the Stanford Conference on Business Education., 1926
  - Stanford Conference on the Humanities, Report of the 1st-4th annual conference held by the Stanford School of Humanities, 1943-46., 1944
  - Stanford Conference on the Humanities (1st: 1943: Stanford, Calif.), The humanities look ahead: "The humanities in the war and postwar world,". (Box 58)
  - Stanford Conference on the Humanities (2nd: 1944: Stanford, Calif.), The humanities chart their course., 1945
  - Stanford Conference on the Humanities (3rd: 1945: Stanford, Calif.), Elementary courses in the humanities., 1946
  - Stanford Symposium on Mathematical Methods in the Social Sciences (1959: Stanford University), Mathematical methods in the social sciences, 1959; proceedings., 1960
  - Stanford University Press, Photolith, Stanford university press; a working manual., 1940
  - Stanford University, Stanford laboratory guides. Biological series., 1926
  - Stanford University. Committee on Scholarship, Report of sub-committee of Committee on Scholarship on student ability., 1923
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Geology, Contributions from the Department of Geology of Stanford University., 1930
  - Stanford University. Food Research Institute, Foundation, organization, general policies, research work in progress, publications., 1923
  - Stanford University. Food Research Institute, Wheat studies of the Food Research Institute., 1924
  - Stanford University. Libraries, A comprehensive exhibition of the writings of W. Somerset Maugham, drawn from various private collections and libraries., 1958
  - Stanford University. Libraries, Finely printed books presented to the Library of Stanford university. A catalogue., 1927
  - Stanford University. School of Medicine, Research work of the Stanford University School of Medicine from 1919 to 1929, with a list of publications.
  - Stanford Workshop on Community Leadership, Report., 1945
  - Starks, Edwin Chapin, 1867-1932, Outline lectures in comparative anatomy and vertebrate zoology., 1928
  - Starks, Edwin Chapin, 1867-1932, The dissection of the dogfish., 1926